(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-12T21:54:25.889748",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
倍の倍のfight 倍倍倍倍 candy tune!
Double of double fight, double, double, double, double candy tune!
本音と建前ない私
Me, without any true feelings or facades...
なりたい 有りたい けどだけど
I want to be, I want to exist, but...
人の目気にせず素直な子
An honest girl who doesn't care about others' opinions...
なりたい 有りたい けどだけど
I want to be, I want to exist, but...
誰かを救うということは 過去の自分も救うことです
To save someone means to save your past self too.
誰かを愛すということは 本当の自分を大好きになることです...
To love someone means to absolutely love your true self.
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイ バイファイ！
Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye, bye fight!
何回転んでも立ち上がれ
No matter how many times you fall, stand back up!
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイ バイファイ！
Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye, bye fight!
厄介な問題も飛び越えろ
Fly over even the most troublesome problems!
嬉しい バイバイ
Happy! Bye bye!
哀しい バイバイ
Sad! Bye bye!
ほら倍の倍の倍の倍でもっと行こうよ
Look, let's go even further with double of double of double of double!
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイ バイファイ！
Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye, bye fight!
飽き性 根性ない状況
A situation with a fickle nature and no guts...
やめたい やめたい けどだけど
I want to quit, I want to quit, but...
もっぱらネガティブ 自虐思考
Mainly negative, self-deprecating thoughts...
やめたい やめたい けどだけど
I want to quit, I want to quit, but...
何かを犠牲にすることは 何かを目指すということです
To sacrifice something means you're aiming for something else.
何かを目指すということは 何かを本気で信じるということです
To aim for something means to truly believe in it.
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイ バイファイ！
Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye, bye fight!
なんてまあ素敵なこの人生
Oh, what a wonderful life this is!
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイ バイファイ！
Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye, bye fight!
だって私はそう私だもん
Because I am simply who I am!
楽しい バイバイ
Fun! Bye bye!
悔しい バイバイ
Regretful! Bye bye!
ほら倍の倍の倍の倍でもっと行こうよ
Look, let's go even further with double of double of double of double!
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイ バイファイ！
Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye, bye fight!
倍の倍のfight 倍倍倍倍 candy tune!
Double of double fight, double, double, double, double candy tune!
自分を大事に 本音を大事に つまずいたって
Value yourself, value your true feelings, even if you stumble,
バイバイファイ！
Bye bye fight!
強い人間になりたかったって？ 今からなれるさ
You wanted to be strong? You can become strong starting right now,
バイバイファイ！
Bye bye fight!
有言実行 言葉に宿った魂信じて
Practice what you preach, believe in the soul within your words,
バイバイファイ！
Bye bye fight!
誰かと比べて落ち込んだって 自分は自分さ
Even if you get depressed comparing yourself to others, you are who you are,
バイバイファイ！
Bye bye fight!
半径100km幸せで満たしたいな
I want to fill a 100km radius with happiness,
バイバイファイ！
Bye bye fight!
生きているだけで凄いことだから命を讃えよう
Just being alive is amazing, so let's celebrate life,
バイバイファイ！
Bye bye fight!
倍倍FIGHT！
Double FIGHT!
バイバイ ほんの小さな一歩
Bye-bye, even a tiny step,
バイバイ 大きな大きな一歩
Bye-bye, a giant, giant step,
バイバイ どれも君にとって
Bye-bye, all of them for you,
大切な 大切な 勇気の証だよ
are precious, precious proofs of your courage!
バイバイ バイババイバイ バイバイバイ
Bye-bye, bye-by-bye-bye, bye-bye-bye!
なんと言われても諦めぬ
No matter what they say, I won't give up!
バイバイ バイババイバイ バイバイバイ
Bye-bye, bye-by-bye-bye, bye-bye-bye!
人生これきり 一度きり
You only live once, this is the only time!
バイバイ バイババイバイ バイバイバイ
Bye-bye, bye-by-bye-bye, bye-bye-bye!
何回転んでも立ち上がれ
No matter how many times you fall, stand back up!
バイバイ バイババイバイ バイバイバイ
Bye-bye, bye-by-bye-bye, bye-bye-bye!
厄介な問題も飛び越えろ
Leap right over any troublesome problems!
嬉しい
Happy!
楽しい
Fun!
ほら 倍の倍の倍の倍でもっと乗り越えよう
Look, let's overcome even more, double by double!
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイバイ
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye-bye!
いっせーのーせっ！ あちちちたのしー！
One, two, three, go! It's so hot and fun!
険しい道もともに歩むんだ
We will walk down the rugged path together!
You will never walk alone
つまずいても もがいて強くなるんだ
Even if we stumble and struggle, we'll get stronger!
Oh, oh, oh...
険しい道もともに歩むんだ
We will walk down the rugged path together!
You will never walk alone
つまずいても もがいて強くなるんだ
Even if we stumble and struggle, we'll get stronger, oh...
明日からじゃなくて今日だ 今だ 君だ ここだ
It's not starting tomorrow—it's today, now, you, here!
弱音吐いて疲れたならちょっと休むかい？
If you're tired from whining, do you want to rest a bit?
私たちがいつもそばにいるからさ
Because we will always be right by your side!
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイバイ
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye-bye!
はーい！キミたちー！
Hi! Everyone!
7周年記念ライブ始まりましたね！
My 7th Anniversary Live has officially begun!
ハッシュタグは、えー、こちら！こちら！こちら！
The hashtag is, uh, this one! This one! This one!
#宝鐘マリン7周年3DLIVE になっております！
It's #HoushouMarine7thAnniversary3DLive!
このあとね、知ってると思うけど、うふ、水着のお披露目が
After this, as you probably already know, ehehe, there's a swimsuit reveal!
ありますので！3D水着！うわー楽しみでしょう？
Yes! 3D swimsuits! Wow, aren't you excited?
いっぱいスクショして、ツイートしてくだ...
Take lots of screenshots and tweet...
ポスト！ポストしてください！
Post! Please post them!
ここから先も、まだまだ、えー、素敵なゲストの皆さん
Moving forward, we still have, uh, many wonderful guests
来ますので、一体どんな曲、どんなパフォーマンスをするのか
coming up! I wonder what kind of songs and performances they'll do...
超超楽しみに！そして水着がどんな感じなのか...
Please look forward to it! And as for what the swimsuits will look like...
差分もいっぱいあるからね！あの差分も全部見切ってから、見切ってくださいね！
There are lots of variations too! Make sure you see all of them!
そして、素敵な、うーん、グッズもね、マリンが
Also, Marine has designed some amazing merchandise
いっぱい考えたグッズとかもありますんで！
that we have available, so please check them out!
さあ！どんどん楽しんでいきましょう！
Now, let's keep having fun!
いくぞーー！
Here we go!
ロンリー ロリロリ神、降臨
Watch the lonely loli goddess now descend.
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
Hear the resounding sound of bells across the land.
これは救済のレクイエム
For your salvation, the band plays this requiem.
せーのっ
Ready?
触ったら逮捕！極chu❤de！点呼！
Touch me, I'll arrest y'all! Lovey-dovey roll call!
1、2、3、4？
One, two, three, four?
ごめんなさーい
We're sorry, miss!
ごめんなさいが聞こえなーい
I couldn't hear your apology!
粛聖！！ロリ神レクイエム☆
Now repent!! It's the godly loli requiem☆
将来は お前なんかに 好かれたくない
When I grow up, I never want to be liked by the likes of you.
泥水で口を洗え
Go wash your mouth out with mud.
法廷で会おう？ねっ
Shall we meet in court? Okay?
さぁ おまわりさん 連れて行って
That's right, officer, take them away.
妄想しか取り柄のない かわいそうな人
All they have going for them is delusions—what a pathetic person.
るーちゃん！るーちゃん！待ってよ るーちゃん！
(Ru-chan! Ru-chan! Wait up, Ru-chan!)
その姿 親に見せられますか？
Would you still behave this way if mom and dad were here too?
るーちゃん！マリンちゃん！かわいいよ！
(Ru-chan! Marine-chan! You're so cute!)
わぁ、ありがとう。お疲れ様です。
Aww, thank you. Good job, everyone.
ロリロリ神、降臨
Now the godly loli has appeared
マジヤバ奴らに用心
Really gotta watch for creeps; don't let 'em near
まともじゃないなら 早く消えてください
If your social conduct's nada, please hurry up and disappear.
Lonely ロリロリ神、降臨
Now the lovely, holy, godly loli's here
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
This bell will ring, I'll sing, dispelling all your fear.
とても優しくて
You are so wonderful...
素敵なお兄ちゃん
...and sweet, dear big brother.
楽園でほら ねんねしな
Heaven's too good for you, bud; sleep in hell, please.
これは救済のレクイエム
For your salvation, the band plays this requiem.
ほら
Look...
なんちゃってなのだ
Just kidding!
ほら、世の中にはこんなに気持ち悪い人たちが蔓延ってるんですよ！
Look at them all. Look at all these disgusting people spreading their degeneracy!
みーんな、晒しageますよ
I'll expose every single one of you.
触ったら逮捕！極chu❤de！点呼！
Touch me, I'll arrest y'all! Lovey-dovey roll call!
1、2、3、4？
One, two, three, four?
ごめんなさーい
We're sorry, miss!
ごめんなさいが聞こえなーい
I couldn't hear your apology!
粛聖！！ロリ神レクイエム☆
Now repent!! It's the godly loli requiem☆
はーい！獄中にいるみなさーん！
Alright! How're my adoring jailbirds doing?
刑務所ファンミーティングのお時間でーす！
It's time for the prison's weekly fan club meeting!
その腐りきった耳をゴリゴリかっぱじって、よーく聞いてくださいね！
So clean out those rotten ears of yours, and listen carefully to what I'm gonna say!
ざーこ！
Nobodies!
キモキモ！
You're disgusting!
たすかる！
This helps!
うるさい
Shut up!
黙ってもらっていいですか？
Could you please be quiet?
嫌いです
I hate you.
かわいそう
How pathetic.
ちっさ、弱っ、みっともな
So small, so weak, how shameful.
どうしようもない お兄ちゃん お姉ちゃん
Hopeless big brothers and big sisters,
もうちょっとまともなこと言えないの？お前ら
can't you guys say something more decent?
汚物消毒110番だー！
Sanitize the filth, call 110!
呼吸結界発動！
Activating breathing barrier!
粛清！
Purge!
ういビーム！
Ui Beam!
もう一丁！
One more time!
ういビーム！
Ui Beam!
まだまだー！
Not done yet!
怒りの心 聖なる雷霆
Heart of wrath, holy thunder...
神殺神罰奇跡を施す
...bestowing deicide and divine punishment miracles.
愚かなる汚れを 骨の髄まで
Purifying foolish impurity down to the marrow...
浄化する一筋の光 それが、ういビーム、なのです！
...with a single ray of light! That is the Ui-Beam!
ういは、すべてを許します
Ui-chan forgives everything.
あーあー この世の醜さを
Ah, ah... I'll gather up all the ugliness of this world...
集めて描いてみるよ
...and try to draw it.
真っ白なダンボール 汚れてない天使
On a pure white cardboard box, an unblemished angel.
ロンリー 振り向いた少女は そっと手を掴む
Lonely, the girl who looked back gently takes my hand.
かくれんぼなどないから
Because there is no hide-and-seek.
大きなお友達のみんなへ
To all my grown-up friends,
お前らが打ち込んでいる虚無には何の意味があるの？
what is the meaning of the void you're dedicating yourselves to?
ねえ、教えてよ
Hey, tell me.
マリン、全然分かんないんだ！
Marine has absolutely no idea!
ロリロリ神降臨
The Loli Loli God descends!
さよなら 笑顔でバイバイ
Goodbye, sayonara with a smile!
フィナーレはお見事
The finale is splendid,
弔って差し上げましょう
let me hold a memorial service for you.
らりらりロリロリ神降臨
Lari lari, the Loli Loli God descends!
あわれな姿ね かわいそうに
What a pitiful sight, how tragic.
とても優しくて 素敵なお兄ちゃん
You are a very kind and wonderful big brother.
楽園でほら ねんねしな
Now go to sleep in paradise.
それが救済の レクイエム
That is the Requiem of Salvation.
せーの、だまらっしゃーい！
One, two, shut up!
服役中で成功！
Success in serving prison time!
1、2、3、4
One, two, three, four!
ごめんなさい？
You're sorry?
ごめんなさいが聞こえない！
I can't hear you say you're sorry!
粛聖ロリ神レクイエム！
Shukusei Rorikami Requiem!
本当に気持ち悪い
You're really disgusting.
マリンちゃん、7周年おめでとう！
Marine-chan, happy 7th anniversary!
じゃ、帰るね
Well, I'm going home now.
あ、およ！
Ah, wait!
ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge？
Throb, throb, wearing rouge?
いきますよ〜！
Here we go!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girls are innocent!
やっぱ キラキラ もっと クラクラ
After all, sparkling! More dizzying!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girls are innocent!
うい！うい！ういも無罪！
Ui! Ui! Ui is also innocent!
ねえ、言ったよね？ 年齢なんて関係ないってさ
Hey, you said it, right? That age doesn't matter.
そういうめんどくさいのも含めて愛してくれるって
That you'd love me, including all those troublesome things.
ねえねえ、言ったよね？言ってない？
Hey, hey, you said it, right? You didn't?
ふーん、そういうこと言うんだ。
Hmph, so that's how you're going to play it.
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？
By the way, on this ship, "Beautiful Girl Innocence" applies, though?
まかせて！魔法で若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenating with magic,
ひみつの素顔はキミにだけ
showing my secret true self only to you...
トクベツですよ〜？
It's special, okay?
ah... アタシ厄介よ
Ah... I'm a handful.
ah... 港なんかじゃ はしゃげないわ近頃はね
Ah... We can't just frolic at any old port these days.
宝の島にしてほしい気分
I'm in the mood for you to make it a treasure island.
出航ーー！！
Set sail!!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice! Beautiful girls are innocent!
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Aiming to be your number one, Yousoro!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃう
Actually, I lack confidence, but I'll do my best!
ahoy！！
Ahoy!!
きゅっきゅっきゅるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurun!
きゅっきゅっきゅるんるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurunrun!
恋する気持ち17才
The feeling of being in love, 17 years old!
0時になっちゃうわ オトナの時間
It's about to hit midnight, adult time!
やっぱ キラキラ もっと クラクラ
After all, sparkling! More dizzying!
ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge？
Throb, throb, wearing rouge?
まだ早い
It's still too early.
だっだっダメですか？ フリルの服着たら
I-I-Is it no good? If I wear frilly clothes...
そんなこと、ないよ
There's no such thing!
だっだっだって 魔法少女になってみたい
B-B-But, I want to try being a magical girl...
ギリギリ有罪！？
Barely guilty!?
進路はなんの星？
What star is our route on?
ちょっぴり足んない積極性？
A little lacking in aggressiveness?
結局キミももっと若い子？
In the end, do you also prefer younger girls?
なんでもするから見捨てないでキミたち！
I'll do anything, so please don't abandon me, everyone!
ちょっと良いトコ見てみたーい！
I want to see a bit of your good side!
ah... たまにいじけちゃう
Ah... sometimes I get sulky.
ah... それでもいいの？
Ah... is that okay with you?
年頃だもん本気にしちゃう
I'm at that age, so I'll take it seriously.
嵐の中も
Even in the middle of a storm,
一緒に、行こう？
shall we go together?
出航ーー！！
Set sail!!
ハートにチャーム美少女無罪
Charm to the heart, beautiful girls are innocent!
あれあれどーした？
Oh my, what's wrong?
めんどくさいなんて言っちゃって
Saying that we are bothersome...
かまってくれるキミが好き
...I love that you still pay attention to us!
ahoy！！
Ahoy!!
きゅっきゅっきゅるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurun!
きゅっきゅっきゅるん きゅっきゅっきゅるんるん
Squeeze, squeeze, cute! Squeeze, squeeze, super cute!
優しくしてね 17歳
Please be gentle with me, I'm 17 years old.
突っ込んで経験値
Dive in deep and get some experience...
お楽しみ
...and look forward to...
チュッ
...a kiss!
ドキドキして
Make my heart throb!
あぁ、お許しくだた～い！
Ah, please forgive me!
このういの魅力！魔力！不可抗力！
This is Ui's charm! Magic! Overwhelming force!
罪な女ね
What a sinful woman, right?
離さないで つかまっていて
Don't let go, hold on tight!
世界の広さ 見せてあげるから
Because I'll show you how wide the world is!
出航！
Set sail!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, beautiful girls are innocent!
キミの 一番 目指して ヨーソロー！
Aiming to be your number one, keep her steady!
冗談も大好きだけど 真剣よ
I love joking around, but I'm being serious!
きゅっきゅっきゅるん きゅっきゅっきゅるんるん
Squeeze, squeeze, cute! Squeeze, squeeze, super cute!
恋する気持ち 17歳
These feelings of love are forever 17!
0時に なっちゃうわ オトナの時間
It's about to strike midnight, the time for adults!
ドキドキして ルージュ
Make my heart throb, with rouge!
まだ早い？
Is it too soon?
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girls are innocent!
マリン！マリン！マリンは無罪！
Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girls are innocent!
うい！うい！ういは無罪！
Ui! Ui! Ui is innocent!
マリン船長と
Captain Marine and...
ういちゃんでしたー！
...Ui-chan!
はぁ〜〜〜〜！
Whew~~~~!
マリンちゃん！ / はぁ〜、ういちゃん！
Marine-chan! / Whew, Ui-chan!
ということで。
And so...
はぁ、疲れました。
Whew, I'm tired.
疲れてる？ / さすが9歳、元気いっぱい。
Are you tired? / As expected of a 9-year-old, so full of energy.
えぇ？ちょっと無理してる。 / あはは、ちょっと無理してる(笑)
Eh? I'm forcing myself a bit. / Ahaha, forcing yourself a bit?
はい、マリンの、9、9歳...間違えた！ / お前も9歳ではない。
Yes, Marine's, 9, 9-year-old... wait, I got it wrong! / You're not 9 years old either!
そうです、マリンの7周年ライブに、ういちゃんが来てくれました！
That's right, Ui-chan came to Marine's 7th anniversary live!
イェーイ！お邪魔します！おめでとう！ / ありがとうございまーす！
Yay! Thank you for having me! Congratulations! / Thank you so much!
なんとね、マリンね、16歳のういとはね、もうめっちゃ、マブ？ / あ、そうなんだ。
You see, Marine and the 16-year-old Ui are already total \"mabus\" (besties)? / Ah, is that so?
なんだけどね、ういちゃんともね、これからマブになっていきたいなって思ってて。初絡みなんですけど、どうぞよろしく！
But I'm hoping to become besties with Ui-chan too from now on. This is our first collab, so please be nice to me!
あ、帰ります。 / ちょっと！待てよ！待てよ！
Ah, I'm going home. / Wait! Hold on! Hold on!
ちょっと、待てよ！
Hold on!
ということでね。 / はい。
And with that... / Yes.
ういちゃん、何か気づかない？
Ui-chan, do you notice anything?
え？露出？ / あ、そこ？興味ある？興味ある？
Eh? The exposure? / Ah, that? Are you interested? Interested?
これね、ういちゃん、あなたの放った「ういビーム」だ！バーン！
This is, Ui-chan, the \"Ui Beam\" you fired! Bam!
ちょっと、あの、新しい設定つけるのやめてください。
Wait, please stop adding new lore to me.
ういビームで服が弾け飛んじゃった。 / そんな効能ありません！
Your Ui Beam blasted my clothes off! / My beam doesn't do that!
っていう感じでね、新衣装となっています。
Anyway, this is my new outfit!
めっちゃ可愛い！なんか、ぬいぐるみついてない？
It's so cute! Wait, is there a plushie attached?
え？そうなの、ついてるの。 / 欲しい、1個もらっていい？
Eh? Yes, there is. / I want one, can I have one?
うわ、すごい9歳っぽい。めっちゃ9。いいよ、ぶちっ。 / おっぱいもあげる、ぶちっ。
Wow, that's so 9-year-old-like. So 9. Sure, here. / I'll give you my boob too. *rip*
いらない。お土産、バイバーイ。 / ちょっと待てよ！待てよ！
No thanks. Thanks for the souvenir, bye! / Wait! Hold on!
見てほら、ここにさ、ほら、「03」。 / あ！本当だ、背中に「03」。
Look, here, look, \"03\". / Ah! You're right, there's \"03\" on your back.
ほら、お尻すっげ。
Look, your butt is amazing.
30じゃないよ！3年目！
It doesn't mean 30! It means 3rd anniversary!
30じゃないよ。
It doesn't mean 30.
いや、ういちゃんね、これね、まだまだ脱げるんで。 / 大丈夫ですか？
Well, Ui-chan, I can take even more off. / Are you going to be okay?
この後にね、これから... / あの、YouTube的に大丈夫ですか？
After this, from now on... / Um, is it okay on YouTube?
髪型とか、服とか、まだまだね、違うのがあるのでね。
There are still different hairstyles and outfits coming up.
みんなね、これで満足して帰らないように。 / 頑張って隠してください。 / まだあるよ、まだまだあるよ。
So everyone, don't leave thinking this is all. / Please do your best to cover up. / There's still more, there's more!
ということで、あとね、選曲の話もしようと思うんですけど。
So, let's also talk about the song choices.
えーっと、ういちゃんとは...
Um, with Ui-chan...
やっぱりね、持ち歌の『ロリ神レクイエム』
After all, your song \"Loli God Requiem\"...
やりましたけど。可愛〜！ / どうでしたか？
We did it! So cute! / How was it?
えっとね、マリン歌ってみたも出してるんですけど。 / 9歳の方ね。
Well, I've also released a cover of it. / The 9-year-old version.
そう、マリンの歌ってみたのバージョンだとめっちゃ「レコイエム！」って感じで歌ってるんだけど。
Yeah, in Marine's cover version, I sang it like \"Requiem!\" in a really crazy voice.
なんて？
What?
「レコイエム！」
\"Requiem!\"
って感じで。かなりおねだり出してたんだけど。
Like that. I put a lot of demand into it.
ま、今回はね、なんかマリンもこの姿のまま「レコイエム！」ってやったらちょっと「あ、」ってなるから。 / 言ってるね、もう今ね。
But this time, if Marine did \"Requiem!\" in this outfit, it would be a bit like \"Oh...\" / You're saying it right now, though.
ここはちょっと真面目にね、普通にいつものマリンで歌わせてもらいました。
So I sang it more seriously, as my usual Marine self.
そっちの方がいいよ。
That's much better.
あ、マリンちゃん。 / なんだよ、なんだよ！
Ah, Marine-chan. / What is it, what is it?
若作りしない方がいいよ。 / なんでよ、もう！やめて。
You shouldn't try so hard to look young. / Why! Come on! Stop it.
あとは...
And also...
あの、ういの方とはね、Kアリーナでういのライブで一緒に歌わせてもらった
Um, I also sang with the other Ui at the K-Arena for her live concert...
歌いましたので。 / やてったね。
We sang that. / We did.
疲れました。 / ふふ、疲れました(笑)
I'm tired. / Fufu, tired? (laughs)
疲れました？いいよもう帰って、疲れましたでしょ。 / じゃ、帰ります。 / 話終わったから。
Are you tired? You can go home now, you must be tired. / Okay, I'll go home then. / Since we're finished talking.
まだまだライブは続くぞ！ / 冷たい！
The live show is still going! / Cold!
まだまだ続く！
It's still going!
レッツゴー！ / バイバイ！
Let's go! / Bye-bye!
応援してね！こんなに求められてないことある？
Please support her! Has anyone ever been wanted this little?
パレード パレード パレード！
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
We're gonna shine!
呼び合う声を合図に
With our calling voices as our signal...
パレード パレード パレード！
Parade, Parade, Parade!
探しにゆく
We'll go on a search...
スタートは何度だって
Our start can be as many times as we want!
手を上げて
Raise your hands!
Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Clap your hands, all the way across the sea!
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it reaches you!
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands!
ほら一緒に Everybody
Come on, together, everybody!
Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Clap your hands, all the way across the sky!
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it resounds!
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands!
光射す 僕たちの未来
To our future where the light shines through!
Are you ready?
コンコンコン Yes こんな狐に化かされて
Kon, kon, kon, yes, being tricked by a fox like this!
Knock, knock, knock 心を開けて
Knock, knock, knock, open up your heart!
Everything's gonna be alrightって感じよ
It feels like everything's gonna be alright!
今、噂の Bewitch you
Right now, the rumored "Bewitch you!"
もう一回！
One more time!
コンコンコン Yes こんな狐に化かされて
Kon, kon, kon, yes, being tricked by a fox like this!
Knock, knock, knock 心を開けて
Knock, knock, knock, open up your heart!
Don't stop music!
ほら朝まで行くよ
Look, we're going until morning!
今、地球の裏にチューニング
Right now, tuning in to the other side of the Earth!
コンコンコン 魔法をかけて
Kon, kon, kon, cast a spell!
飽きるまで Be with you
Until we grow tired of it, I'll be with you!
ねぇもっと！好きになってもらいたいの
Hey, more! I want you to love me more!
頭の中は君ばっかり！
My head is filled only with thoughts of you!
ってゆーかそっぽなんて向いてないで
I mean, don't look away from me!
あぁもう！ヤキモキしちゃうんだからぁ！
Ah, geez! You're making me so anxious!
ずっとずっと好きがいいの
I want us to love each other forever and ever!
心の奥もっともっとトキめいちゃうくらいに
So much that the depths of my heart flutter even more!
こっち向いててよねたまに
Look at me once in a while, okay?
もう離さないから
Because I won't let you go anymore!
絶対に
Absolutely!
Love you love you Oh
I love you Oh
Ah...
つまらないデイズもう散散ね！
Boring days are already over!
奇跡願っているだけの人世
A life spent just wishing for miracles...
Watch me do...
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Magic with no secret tricks or spells!
I wanna be free! だってまだふりだし
I wanna be free! Because I'm still at the start!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って drivin'
Jumping into a playful carriage and drivin'
あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
I'm undergoing a great transformation, make-up!
我儘のままに燦きに注意
Shining as selfishly as I want, watch out!
洒落た街で dancin'
Dancing in a stylish town!
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
So then, goodbye inferiority complex!
何時かは喝采クラップオウデエエンス
Someday, applause from the clapping audience!
皆々御唱和あれ！
Everyone, sing along!
Bibbidi bobbidi boowa
Bibbidi bobbidi boowa Yeah
物語があってもしようがない
It's no use even if there's a story...
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう
Then those who dance freely are the winners, right?
失礼しますが、死んでください
Excuse my rudeness, but could you please die?
Killin' the base!
こんなことが楽しい
Knowing this is so much fun!
Hit the pitch!
So fucking 可愛い
So fucking cute!
可愛いね
Cute, isn't it?
See you later, 先生！さようなら adieu!
See you later, sensei! Goodbye, adieu!
Killin' the base to get 'em to say alright
絶景なアンサー soldiers
Brilliant answer, soldiers!
Dead beats, listen up, it's what you want me... Got 'em, got 'em...
カプセルやってる地獄で犯罪じゃないから
Doing capsules in hell isn't a crime!
うるさいよ
Shut up!
We'll dance anyway 'cause it's human age!
聞いてよ そこのあなたも 何となく一緒に楽しもう
Listen up, you over there, let's just enjoy together!
あなたの新しい日々に
To your new everyday life!
申し訳ないです、やりすぎました。なんでキトリラプしてる、ちょっと変だ
I'm sorry, I went too far. Why am I speed rapping, it's a bit weird.
一切合切 お任せあれ Doggy Doggy god
Leave everything entirely to us, doggy doggy god!
Oh yeah!
憂犬群青 バイバイベイベー Doggy Doggy god
Blue dog pack, bye bye baby, doggy doggy god!
Oh yeah!
当然今日も疾風怒濤 Doggy Doggy god
Naturally today too, swift and stormy, doggy doggy god!
Oh yeah!
Clap your hands, wag your tail, on & on & on & on
Bow-wow-wow! Louder than words, ありのままさ
Bow-wow-wow! Louder than words, just as we are!
ワンワンワンダー ダーダーダーフルな この生き様
Wan-wan-wonder, da-da-daful way of living!
掴んだら 離さない One chance で輝く
Once you grab it, don't let go, shining in one chance!
I'm a 絶対的霊験あらたかな Doggy god
I'm an absolute, miraculous doggy god!
ああ、混沌情報過多のレストランで
Ah, at the restaurant of chaotic information overload...
うそっぱちのメニューにお茶こぼして
...spilling tea on a lying menu!
君ともぐもぐ
Chewing with you...
もぐもぐ
Mogu mogu...
銃撃戦の真ん中でもぐもぐ
...chewing even in the middle of a gunfight!
魑魅魍魎腹ペコの群れ
A starving crowd of monsters...
満腹になる未来を願っているよ
...hoping for a future where we are full!
もぐもぐ
Mogu mogu...
世界が終わる前に
...before the world ends!
もぐもぐYUMMY！ マジ神
Mogu Mogu YUMMY! Seriously godlike!
ヤムヤム ありのまんま
Yum yum, just the way it is!
もぐもぐYUMMY！ magic coming
Mogu Mogu YUMMY! Magic coming!
この世を味わうんだ うまうま
Tasting this world, delicious delicious!
Sexy 世界一 Super ピチピチ
Sexy, world's number one, super fresh!
Sexy世界一 Superピチピチ
Sexy number one, super fresh
ぶっちゃけ船長捕まえたくない？
Don't you honestly want to capture the Captain?
You're gonna get the treasure Maybe tasting me
私の甘さが欲しいでしょ
Don't you want my sweetness?
秘宝の鍵を
The key to the secret treasure...
優しく刺して
...gently insert it.
宝庫の扉
The door of the vault...
マジで早く開けて
...hurry up and open it!
自覚ないでしょうね 思い通りに
You probably don't realize... that just as I planned...
君は動かされていること
...you are being manipulated.
単純じゃないの 駆け引きのヒント
It's not simple, so pick up...
すべて拾って
...every single clue in this game.
唯一無二の条件 提示することで
By presenting these unique conditions...
理解できた 愛のカタチも
...I was finally able to understand the shape of love.
毒か薬かの微熱に 狂わされていても
Even if you are driven mad by this slight fever, be it poison or medicine...
最後に笑う 君と
...you will be the one laughing in the end.
Million, Million... 加速していく
Million, Million... it keeps accelerating.
Million, Million... 果てにいこうか
Million, Million... shall we go to the very end?
Million, Million... 鮮烈に満ちる
Million, Million... vividly filling...
ビビッドなステージへ
...the vivid stage!
あこがれの 舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage of my dreams
らしく輝きたい
I want to shine as myself
ときに涙して
Sometimes shedding tears
また笑い合いたい
I want to laugh together again
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手に入れたい
I want to get that dream
ふみだそう 奇跡の一歩を
Let's take a miraculous step forward!
いききらして夢追いかけたい
Out of breath, I want to chase my dreams
わくわく止まらない
The excitement won't stop
そうさそうさ 超えてゆく
That's right, that's right, going beyond...
世界に見せてあげる
...I'll show it to the world
アクセスしてみたい？
Do you want to access it?
後悔なんてここにない
There are no regrets here
それじゃ、これで
Well then, with this...
決まった？
...is it decided?
心で
With our hearts...
つながる
...we are connected!
はーい注目 まあいっちょ踊ってこうか？
Hey, pay attention, let's dance another round, shall we?
視線牛耳ってんのは… III
Who's holding all the gazes... III!
あれ～？君たちの声 まだ足りてないんじゃないの～？
Huh~? Your voices, aren't you still lacking energy~?
Our night's just begun. Aye let's blast it!
赤くほてるface
A face flushed red
ヒートアップしちゃって絡むsweat
Sweat tangling up as we heat up
乾いた喉潤す
Quenching a thirsty throat
オアシスよマリンブルー
An oasis of Marine Blue
あっはーん！たまらないんでしょ？
Ahaaan! Isn't it irresistible?
From shore to shore
I'm gonna get your ass on the dance floor
We're kicking off over L.A.
Miami, New York, step to the rhythm
And you ready for more?
If you want to bump my shine
Boy, go get your sunglasses on
I can make it rain when I hit the jackpot, baby
Get ready if you want to ride on with Kobo
あーうっちちな二人はだあれ？
Hey, who are those two hot people?
Hands up ぶち上げたまえ！
Hands up, pump it up!
クラッときちゃう様な熱が足りない
Lacking the kind of heat that makes you dizzy
Our night's just begun. Aye let's blast it!
ハジけて派手にいったーれ！
Burst out and go wild in style!
来世まで we wanna party
We wanna party till the next life
All eyes on me
I can taste the high
Aye まだまだ沸いてこうぜ
Aye, let's keep getting hyped up!
はーい注目 まあいっちょ踊ってこうか？
Hey, pay attention, let's dance another round, shall we?
視線牛耳ってんのは… III
Who's holding all the gazes... III!
ねえ、近寄ってよ
Hey, come closer...
このお宝ボックス開けるの？
...are you gonna open this treasure box?
焦らさないでよ
Don't tease me...
キミのことが欲しいんだわ
...because I want you!
Aku mau kamu ada di sini bersamaku
I want you to be here with me
Bring in the heat that can't be splashed away
Fishing a big catch, the stardom I deserve, but I'm just chilling
A mocktail mai tai, sipping 'cause I got that juice
Might let you have a taste
この身体で
With this body...
Let me look at your body
魅惑する肌に
...this charming skin
Let me look at your body
Start a bonfire
Our luring smoke takes you higher
ねえ？ We'll drive you crazy
Right? We'll drive you crazy
熱苦しくなってこう
Let's get all hot and bothered!
もうどうしようもない
Already helpless,
my bright spotlight
どんどん新境地イッちゃいそう？
Are we heading further into new territory?
あーぅチチな二人はだぁれ？
Who are the two super hot ones?
hands up ぶち上げたまえ！
Hands up, pump it up!
クラッときちゃう様な 熱が足りない
Not enough heat to make you dizzy.
our night's just begun aye let's blast it!
Our night has just begun, aye, let's blast it!
ハジけて派手にいったーれ！
Burst out and go wild!
来世まで we wanna party
We wanna party until the next life.
all eyes on me, I can taste the high
aye
まだまだ沸いてこうぜ
let's keep heating things up!
はーい注目
Listen up, everyone!
まあいっちょ踊ってこうか？
Shall we dance once more?
視線牛耳ってんのは… III
The one ruling over your gaze is... III
はーい注目
Listen up, everyone!
まあいっちょ踊ってこうか？
Shall we dance once more?
視線牛耳ってんのは… III
The one ruling over your gaze is... III
ほら！君たちの声、まだ足りてないんじゃないのー？
Hey! Your voices, aren't they still not enough?
our night's just begun, aye let's blast it!
Our night has just begun, aye, let's blast it!
赤く火照る face
A red, glowing face.
ヒートアップしちゃって light up the place
Heating up, light up the place.
乾いた喉潤すオアシスさマリンブルー
Oasis that quenches a dry throat, Marine Blue.
ah-ha! たまらないんだろ？
Ah-ha! You can't resist, right?
from shore to shore
I'm gonna get your ass on the dance floor
we're taking over L.A., Miami, New York
a slave to the rhythm and you're ready for more
if you wanna block my shine? go get your sunblock
I can make it rain when I hit the jackpot
baby, get ready
if you wanna ride on with the OGs
あーぅチチな二人はだぁれ？
Who are the two super hot ones?
hands up ぶち上げたまえ！
Hands up, pump it up!
クラッときちゃう様な 熱が足りない
Not enough heat to make you dizzy.
our night's just begun aye let's blast it!
Our night has just begun, aye, let's blast it!
ハジけて派手にいったーれ！
Burst out and go wild!
来世まで we wanna party
We wanna party until the next life.
all eyes on me, I can taste the high
aye
まだまだ沸いてこうぜ
let's keep heating things up!
はーい注目
Listen up, everyone!
まあいっちょ踊ってこうか？
Shall we dance once more?
視線牛耳ってんのは… III
The one ruling over your gaze is... III
she got the gyatt
now let me see you work with all of that
can you call a doctor 'cause
this baddie's giving me a heart attack
but you know what's scary to me
holo make girls look like Halle Berry to me
Holo makes girls look like Halle Berry to me.
I'm— 2 bars from being canceled
I'm— two bars from being canceled,
so I gotta leave you ever so carefully
bring in the heat that can't be splashed away
fishing a big catch, the stardom I deserve
but I'm just chilling
Courvoisier, I'm sipping
'cause I got that juice
and I might let you have a taste
この身体で
With this body...
let me rock your body
秘宝な素肌に
On my precious bare skin,
now put that camera on me
beside a bonfire
our luring smoke takes you higher
ね？ we drive you crazy
See? We drive you crazy.
熱苦しくなってこう
Let's make it stiflingly hot.
もうどうしようもない
Already helpless,
my bright spotlight
どんどん新境地イッちゃいそう？
Are we heading further into new territory?
あーぅチチな二人はだぁれ？
Who are the two super hot ones?
hands up ぶち上げたまえ！
Hands up, pump it up!
クラッときちゃう様な 熱が足りない
Not enough heat to make you dizzy.
our night's just begun aye let's blast it!
Our night has just begun, let's blast it!
ハジけて派手にいったーれ！
Burst out and go wild!
来世まで we wanna party
We wanna party until the next life.
all eyes on me, I can taste the high
aye
まだまだ沸いてこうぜ
let's keep heating things up!
はーい注目
Listen up, everyone!
まあいっちょ踊ってこうか？
Shall we dance once more?
視線牛耳ってんのは… III
The one ruling over your gaze is... III
bring it back, let's hit it one last time!
aye 俺らさ、マジで最強じゃん？
Aye, we're seriously the strongest, right?
just two besties so fly!
ah-ah-ah
IRIS OUT
[Song: IRIS OUT]
ダメダメダメ脳髄の中から
No, no, no, from inside my brain...
やめろ馬鹿ともがくモラリティー
Stop it, idiot, struggling morality.
Darlin' baby darlin'
半端なクラフトきらめき 明日紡ぐフィロソフィー
a half-baked craft glitter, philosophy woven tomorrow.
死ぬほど可愛い 上目遣い
Deadly cute upturned eyes...
何が琴線に触れるかしら
What will touch your heartstrings?
ただの心臓 息をするバラバラ鳴る頭とこの身体
Just a heart breathing... my head and body falling apart.
Hey look at her I love you お気に召して IRIS OUT
Hey, look at her, I love you. Please like it, IRIS OUT.
どうしよう
What should I do?
この思いを どうしよう
What should I do with this feeling?
アバラの奥 頭が融けてギャラリーになりそうさ
Deep in my ribs, my head melts and turns into a gallery.
どうしよう 立ち竦んで 溺れ死にそうだ
What should I do, standing frozen, about to drown to death.
今この世で君だけ大正解
Right now, in this world, only you are the perfect answer!
誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？
Who? Who? Who? Who?
ひっくり返っても勝ち目ない
Even if things turn upside down, you have no chance of winning!
君だけルールは適用外
You're the only one exempt from the rules!
イエスと申すはこれしかない
There's no option but to say yes!
カツアゲ放題！
Free to extort you as much as I want!
君が笑顔で放ったアッパー
The uppercut you threw with a smile...
だけでダブラダブラ
...was enough to make me double over.
おでこにスティグマ 申し訳ねえな
A stigma on my forehead, I'm so sorry!
突いて 刺して 射抜いて 突いて
Thrust, stab, shoot through, thrust!
ここ弱点？
Is this your weak point?
死ぬほど可愛いお目々ちゃん
To-die-for cute eyes,
なびく私風に揺れるくらい
fluttering and swaying in my wind.
ハラマクランシン
Haramaku Ranshin!
気づけば当然 この世に生まれた君が悪い
Before you know it, of course, it's your fault for being born into this world!
パチモンでもいい何でもいい
A knockoff is fine, anything is fine!
今君と交わしてるすべて欲しい
I want everything we're sharing right now!
頸動脈からアイラブユー吹き出して
An "I love you" gushing from my carotid artery...
あ、あ、あ、アイリスアウト！
A-A-A-Iris Out!
一体どうしよう この想いをどうしよう あばらの奥を
What on earth should I do? What should I do with these feelings deep inside my ribs?
脳みそが溶けて ゲロになりそう
My brain is melting, I feel like throwing up!
堂々 股開いて 溺れ死にそう
Grandly spreading my legs, feeling like drowning!
今この世で君だけ大正解！
Right now, in this world, only you are the perfect answer!
ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン
Darling, Darling, Darling, Darling...
誰？誰？誰？誰？誰？誰？
Who? Who? Who? Who? Who? Who?
誰！ 誰！ 誰ーー！
Who! Who! Whoooo!
やったー！こぼー！
Yay! Kobo!
おめでとうー！
Congratulations!
ありがとう、こぼ！
Thank you, Kobo!
イエーイ、ハッピーアニバーサリー！
Yay, happy anniversary!
そうそうそうそう、7周年、70周年だったらいいよね
Yes, yes, yes! 7th anniversary... it'd be great if it was the 70th!
かわちい、かわちい！
So cute, so cute!
ちょっとフード似てるよ、ほら、ね、似てるね。
Our hoods look a bit similar. See? They do, right?
似てる？ / 似てる！
Do they? / They do!
似てる、ほら、これフード。どう？フード。
They do. See? This is the hood. How is it?
うん、コボもフードありますよ。 / え？
Yeah, Kobo has a hood too! / Eh?
これ！ / どれ？どこや？
This! / Which one? Where?
う、埋まってる！被れないだろそれ！
It's buried! You can't even wear that!
あ、かわちいね。 / え、どう？どこが可愛い？
So cute. / So, what do you think is cute?
めっちゃセクシー、なんか、お、スイムスーツでしょ？ / あ、そう、スイムスーツ！
Very sexy, like, a swimsuit, right? / Ah, yes, swimsuit!
あー、セクシー！水着可愛い。コボもこのスイムスーツ欲しい！
Ah, sexy! The swimsuit is so cute. Kobo wants this swimsuit too!
あ、欲しい？ / うん、なんかコボはリボン好き。 / リボン？どのリボン？
Oh, you do? / Yeah, Kobo likes ribbons. / Ribbons? Which one?
この、いや、見た、あー、リボンはこれ。 / これ？ここ？
This... well... Ah, the ribbon is this one. / This? Here?
ちっちゃいけど。 / あ、ちっちゃリボン。 / 見ちゃダメ、見ちゃダメ。
It's small, though. / Ah, tiny ribbon. / Don't look, don't look!
綺麗！すごい！
Beautiful! Amazing!
あ、こっちも。 / あ、そうそうそう、これ。リボン、リボン。
This side too. / Ah, yes, yes, yes, this! Ribbon, ribbon.
めっちゃ可愛い、このリボンが。わー！あー！
So cute, this ribbon. Wow! Ah!
え、待って、リボンとお尻、どっちが可愛い？
Wait, which is cuter, the ribbon or my butt?
もっと、もっとシェイク、シェイク。 / もっとシェイク？
Shake it more, shake it! / Shake it more?
うわー！うわー！
Whoa! Whoa!
たすかる。 / コボ, もっとさ、脱いでるの見たいでしょ？
This is a blessing. / Kobo, you want to see me strip more, right?
あ、あの、これ、パッ、パッ。 / え、ダメだよ。 / ダメ？まあいいや。脱いで、脱いでくれる。
Ah, well, this... bam, bam. / Wait, that's not allowed. / Not allowed? Oh well. I'll take it off for you.
え！見せてあげる、コボ。 / だ、大丈夫ですか？え、大丈夫ですか？
Eh! I'll show you, Kobo. / A-Are you sure it's okay? Is it okay?
楽しみに待ってて。 / 大張夫ですか？え？
Look forward to it! / Is it really okay? Eh?
見て！ / いやー！やばい！やばい！
Look! / Nooo! Oh my god! Oh my god!
コボ見て、コボ見て。 / やばい！わー！わー！わー！セクシーレディ！
Kobo look, Kobo look. / Oh my god! Wow! Wow! Wow! Sexy lady!
わー！ちる！
Wow, chill!
もういい、服着るわ。服着る。 / やべえ。
Alright, I'll put my clothes back on. / Crazy.
BANされないようにね。 / やべえ、子供...
We don't want to get banned. / Crazy, kids...
ということで... / 子供み、子供、ノードン、ノードンルック...
And with that... / Kids... kids, no, don't look, don't look!
あ、もう着た、もう着た、ほら、じゃーん。 / あー！すごい！
Ah, I'm wearing them now. See? Ta-da! / Ah! Amazing!
大丈夫。 / これセーフ、セーフ。 / セーフ！ / あ、すごい。
We're safe. / This is safe, safe. / Safe! / Ah, amazing.
で、今日はね、あの、アイアイアイのね...
And today, we did 'I'm Your Treasure Box'...
そう、楽しかった！ / 楽しかった！
Yes, it was so much fun! / It was fun!
お、マリン、お尻... / チュチュチュチュ... / あー、ねー！
Oh, Marine, your butt... / *shaking* / Ah, hey!
And like, today, I I I is synthwave version!
And like, today, 'I'm Your Treasure Box' is the synthwave version!
そう、そうなの！すごいカッコいいバージョンにさせてもらって、カバーさせてもらいました。
Yes, exactly! We got to do a super cool version, we did a cover of it.
めっちゃかっこいい。 / カッコいいバージョンありがとうございます。 / You did a great job with the cover, damn!
Super cool. / Thank you for the cool version! / You did a great job with the cover, damn!
マリンの英語のラップどうだった？
How was Marine's English rap?
She got the cat, now let me see you work with all of that.
She got the cat! / She got the cat! / Yeah, cat! / Get! / Yeah!
Now let me see you work with all of that!
うまっ！ / Yeah, yeah, yeah! / Come on, come on! / Now let me see you work with all of that!
So good! / Yeah, yeah, yeah! / Come on, come on! / Now let me see you work with all of that!
で、何？ん？ / Now let me see you work with all of that!
And what? Huh? / Now let me see you work with all of that!
えー！それは英語ですか？！ / 英語です！ / マリグリッシュですね。
Eh! Is that English?! / It is English! / It's Mariglish!
Can, can you call a doctor?
Cuz this butt is about to give me a heart attack!
がんばったなー！ / イエーイ！ / 偉い、偉い、がんばったなー！ / 英語... / 英語。
You did so well! / Yay! / Good job, good job, you worked hard! / English... / English.
英語、うん、がんばった。 / がんばった、やったー！
English, yeah, I did my best. / You did great, yay!
続きますので、ぜひ見ていってください！
We have more coming up, so please stick around and watch!
コボもありがとー！
Thank you too, Kobo!
うわっ！重っ！
Whoa, heavy!
おい、やったな！
Hey, you did it now!
死んだ。
I'm dead.
Dead.
お別れしたのはもっと 前のことだったような
It seems like it was a long time ago that we said goodbye,
悲しい光は閉じ込めて 踵すり減らしたんだ
keeping the sad light inside, wearing out my heels.
君といた時は見えた 今は見えなくなった
When I was with you I could see it, now I can't.
透明な彗星をぼんやりと でもそれだけ探している
I'm looking for a comet, a transparent comet, but that's all I'm looking for.
しょっちゅう唄を歌ったよ
I often sang a song,
その時だけのメロディーを
a melody just for that moment.
寂しくなんかなかったよ
I wasn't lonely,
ちゃんと寂しくなれたから
because I was able to properly feel lonely.
いつまでどこまでなんて
No matter how far or how long,
正常か異常かなんて
whether it's normal or abnormal...
考える暇も無い程 歩くのは大変だ
Walking is so tough, I don't even have time to think.
楽しい方がずっといいよ
Having fun is much better,
ごまかして笑っていくよ
so I'll keep on faking a smile.
大牢不だ あの痛みは 忘れたって消えやしない
I'll be fine; even if I forget that pain, it will never fade away.
理想で作った道を 現実が塗り替えていくよ
Reality is overwriting the road I paved with ideals.
思い出はその軌跡の上で 輝きになって残っている
And my memories are left glittering upon the path I've taken.
お別れしたのは何で 何のためだったんだろうな
Why did we part ways? What were we trying to accomplish?
悲しい光が僕の影を 前に長く伸ばしている
That sorrowful light is extending my shadow far ahead of me.
時々熱が出るよ
Sometimes I catch a fever,
時間がある時眠るよ
and I sleep whenever I have time.
夢だと解るその中で
Knowing it's just a dream,
君と会ってからまた行こう
I'll set off with you again after we meet.
晴天とはほど遠い
Though we're far from fair weather,
終わらない暗闇にも
and in this unending darkness,
星を思い浮かべたなら すぐ銀河の中だ
if we picture the stars, we're instantly in the galaxy.
あまり泣かなくなっても
Even if we don't cry as much anymore,
靴を新しくしても
and even if we wear new shoes,
大丈夫だ あの痛みは 忘れたって消えやしない
we'll be fine; even if I forget that pain, it will never fade away.
伝えたかった事が
Surely there was something
きっとあったんだろうな
I wanted to tell you.
おそらくありきたりなんだろうけど こんなにも
It was probably really cliché, but even so...
お別れした事は
The fact that we said goodbye
出会った事と繋がっている
is connected to our meeting.
あの透明な彗星は 透明だから無くならない
That transparent comet, because it's transparent, it will never disappear.
〇×どれかなんて
"Yes," "no," or "maybe,"
皆と比べてどうかなんて
comparing ourselves with others...
確かめる間も無い程 生きるのは最高だ
Living is so great, we don't even have time to check.
あまい泣かなくなっても
Even if we don't cry as much anymore,
ごまかして笑っていくよ
we'll just fake it and keep smiling.
大丈夫だ あの痛みは 忘れたって消えやしない
We'll be fine; even if we forget that pain, it will never fade away.
大丈夫だ この光の 始まりには
We'll be fine, because at the source of this light...
君がいる
...you are there.
私は、わたしの事が好き。
I love who I am.
朝起きて 今日は何しよう
What should I do today when I wake up?
好奇心抑えらんない
I can't hold back my curiosity.
踊り出すハートは制御不可能
My dancing heart is completely out of control.
テンプレは丸めて捨てて
Crumple up the templates and throw them away,
スキップで踏んづけちゃおう
and let's step on them with a skip!
地球全部塗り替えちゃおう
Let's repaint the entire Earth!
カチコチはだるいしまじ無理！
Being stiff is so tiresome, seriously no way!
そんなんソッコーイチ抜け！
I'm dropping out of that instantly!
あっかんべーなんだが
Even if I make a funny face,
上等！
bring it on!
心拍数上げて生きようよ
Let's raise our heart rates and live life!
退屈奪って行こうよ
Let's go steal away the boredom!
ウザイのも沼って
Even the annoying things will become a trap,
好きになっちゃうよ☆
and you'll end up falling in love! ☆
完璧キャラ無理ゲー知らんぷり
Pretending not to notice that perfect is impossible.
可愛すぎちゃってグランプリ
Winning the Grand Prix for being way too cute!
Ah 何でも知りたい味見したい
Ah, I want to know everything, I want a taste!
誰も止められやしない
Nobody can stop me!
歌わずにはいられない
I can't help but sing!
もしもで諦めるより
Rather than giving up on "what ifs"...
もしもでBETかましたい
I'd rather place a bet on "what ifs"!
この世界知らない方が損じゃん？
Isn't it a loss not to know this world?
疲れたらちょっとサボって
If you get tired, slack off a bit,
糖分で回復して
and recover with some sugar,
自分の機嫌取ろう
to cheer yourself up!
優等生演じてても無理！
Even acting like a model student is impossible!
ナチュラルで愛らしい乙女なんだが
I'm just a natural, lovely maiden,
最強！
but I'm the strongest!
大好き囲まれて生きようよ
Let's live surrounded by things we love!
明日も笑っていたいよ
I want to keep smiling tomorrow too!
知っちゃったら
Once you get to know me,
そのまま好きになっちゃうぜ☆
you'll fall in love with me just like that! ☆
妄想キャパ無限
My delusional capacity is infinite!
上げてくし頂上だって連れてくし
I'm going up, and I'll take you to the top!
Ah いつでも無茶ぶり攻めの姿勢
Ah, always making reckless demands, an aggressive stance!
誰も止められやしない
Nobody can stop me!
踊らずにはいられない
I can't help but dance!
下向いているそこの君
Hey you there, looking down,
不満ばかり溢しても意味ないじゃんバカ
complaining all the time is meaningless, you dummy!
リセットは無し一度きり
There's no reset, you only get one shot.
いつでも真剣勝負ギリギリ
Always a serious battle to the very limit.
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more,
ワガママになろうぜ！君の人生☆
let's be selfish! It's your life! ☆
我慢とかしなくていい
You don't need to hold back,
そばにいる
I'll be right by your side,
今もこれからもずっと
now and forevermore!
約束
I promise!
心拍数上げて生きようよ
Let's raise our heart rates and live life!
退屈奪って行こうよ
Let's go steal away the boredom!
ウザイのも沼って
Even the annoying things will become a trap,
好きになっちゃうよ☆
and you'll end up falling in love! ☆
完璧キャラ無理ゲー知らんぷり
Pretending not to notice that perfect is impossible.
可愛すぎちゃってグランプリ
Winning the Grand Prix for being way too cute!
Ah 何でも知りたい味見したい
Ah, I want to know everything, I want a taste!
誰も止められやしない
Nobody can stop me!
歌わずにはいられない
I can't help but sing!
コンプレックス♡プリンセス
Complex Princess
La La La La La La La La
一瞬記憶が錯乱するが 恋は恋だ
My memory gets confused for a split second, but love is love.
お楽しみボディ
An exciting body,
愛のボランティア 撫でますドンッ!!
Volunteer of love, I'll stroke you with a BAM!!
どす恋 辛い
Heavy-weight love is painful.
圧倒的な母性と (君たちー♡)
With overwhelming motherly love... (For all of you! ♡)
勝手に進む 年齢 (止められねんだよ!)
And my age which keeps advancing... (You can't stop it!)
鳴らない鐘を 鳴らしましょう
Let's ring the bell that doesn't ring.
私だけを見てくれますか?
Will you look only at me?
ねえ♡
Hey...
好き 好き 好き 好き 片想い
Love, love, love, love, one-sided love!
めちゃめちゃめちゃめちゃ描いたフューチャー
The future we drew so, so, so, so much.
大事に大事にして ダーリン
Treasure me, treasure me, darling!
コンプレックスプリンセス
Complex Princess.
宜しくお願いします
Please treat me well.
コンプレックスプリンセス
Complex Princess!
La La La La La La La La
コンプレックスプリンセス
Complex Princess!
La La La La La La La La
SEXY & CUTIE
全部見せたい 今会いたい
I want to show you everything, I want to see you now.
(ようこそ! マリンワールドへ!!)
(Welcome to Marine World!!)
運命共同体 一心同体 側にいたい
Shared fate, two bodies, one soul, I want to be by your side.
(流石に寂しいわ! 愛されたい!!)
(Naturally I'm lonely! I want to be loved!!)
恋愛 不器用 まである
I might even be clumsy at love.
ぶっちゃけ 嫉妬の申し子 (膝から崩れ落ちる)
To be honest, I'm a child of jealousy (falling to my knees).
ずっと17歳 もっと愛しなさい
Always 17 years old, love me more!
夢が大きくて ごめんなさい
Sorry that my dreams are so big!
ほら♡
Look...
好き 好き 好き 好き 気付いて
Love, love, love, love, notice me!
ててて絆を 思い出して
Remember our strong, strong bond!
熱々圧力 女子力
Hot, hot pressure, girl power!
自己肯定低い お姫様
A princess with low self-esteem,
お迎えに来て 王子様
come pick me up, Prince Charming!
Ah... 時には ヘラる時もあるけど
Ah... sometimes I get emotionally unstable, but...
シナジー全開 海より深い恋心 認知して!
Synergy at full throttle! Acknowledge my love, deeper than the ocean!
(聞こえておりますでしょうかー!?)
(Can you hear me!?)
Ahoy!
ヨーソロー!
Yousoro!
出航!!
Set sail!!
ねえ♡
Hey...
好き 好き 好き 好き 片想い
Love, love, love, love, one-sided love!
めちゃめちゃめちゃめちゃ描いたフューチャー
The future we drew so, so, so, so much.
大事に大事にして ダーリン
Treasure me, treasure me, darling!
コンプレックスプリンセス
Complex Princess.
キミを幸せにします
I will make you happy.
コンプリートプリンセス
Complete Princess!
恋する乙女
A maiden in love.
コンプリートプリンセス
Complete Princess!
生まれ変わるの
I will be reborn...
キミのプリンセス
As your princess.
と、いうわけで！なんと！ツクヨミで大人気のカグラナナさんに来てもらいましたー！
And with that, what do you know! We have the incredibly popular Kagura Nana-san from Tsukuyomi here with us!
イェーイ！カグラー！カグラー！カグヤ？カグヤちゃうカグラ！
Yay! Kagura! Kagura! Kaguya? Not Kaguya, Kagura!
えー可愛い、可愛い、可愛いですね！
Ah, cute, cute, you're cute!
まぁところでですね、初絡みなので、お互いの呼び方とか決めたいんですけど。
By the way, since this is our first time collabbing, I'd like us to decide what to call each other.
おっ、おっ、おっと、ねぇ。カグラは…カグラ、うん。
Oh, oh, oh, I see. Kagura is... Kagura, yeah.
あ、カグラ、カグラですね。じゃあマリンのこと、マリンでもいいし船長でもいいんですけど、まぁ何でもOKです。
Ah, Kagura, Kagura it is. Then, as for Marine, "Marine" is fine, "Senchou" is fine too, anything is okay.
じゃあ、えー、マリンって呼ぶね。
Then, I'll call you Marine.
ぐはっ、食らったー！くら、くら、食らったー！きゃー可愛い！
Argh, I got hit! I got hit, hit, hit! Kyah, so cute!
いやマリン、今日呼んでくれてありがとう！
Thank you for inviting me today, Marine!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
え、すごいよこんな大きく素敵ステージで歌えてさ、もうテンションも爆上げって感じ。超楽しかった！
Wow, it's amazing to sing on such a big and wonderful stage, my tension is super high! It was so much fun!
ああ、良かったですー！
Ah, I'm glad to hear that!
でさ、マリンは活動7周年なんだよね？
And Marine, you are celebrating your 7th anniversary of activities, right?
そうなんです！
That's right!
おめでとう！ ありがとう…
Congratulations! Thank you...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
いや、7年ですよ、7年。
Well, it's 7 years, 7 years.
すげぇ！
Incredible!
いや、カグラはまだまだ新人だと思うんですけど、ちょっとね…
Well, I think Kagura is still a newcomer, but...
ね、ね。カグラも末永く7年、いや、それを超える10年、末永く活動してください！
Yeah, yeah. Please keep doing activities for a long time too, 7 years, or even beyond that, 10 years!
あたりまえじゃない、一生やるぞ！
Of course, I'll do this for life!
一生やってくれ、カグラ！ありがとう！マリンとカグラ、一生やるぞ！
Do it for life, Kagura! Thank you! Marine and Kagura, we'll do this for life!
やるぞ！一生行くぞ、一生行くぞ、マリン、マリン行くぞ！エイ、エイ、オー！
We'll do it! Let's go for life, let's go for life! Marine, Marine is going! Ei, ei, oh!
どういうテンションやねん。
What kind of high energy is this...
ま、それは置いておいてですね、まぁ今日ね、選曲の話もさせていただきたいと思います。
Well, setting that aside, I'd like to talk about the song selection today.
えー、カグラのオリジナル曲「私は私のことが好き」と、マリンのオリジナル曲「コンプレックス♡プリンセス」をデュエットしました！
We performed a duet of Kagura's original song "I Like Myself" and Marine's original song "Complex Princess"!
しました！
We did!
私はね、このかぐやの感情豊かな歌声が大好きで
I really love Kaguya's emotional singing voice.
歌唱力が高いだけじゃなく、表現力まで凄いし...
Not only is your singing ability great, but your expressiveness is amazing too...
本当に元気の出る曲、一緒に歌えて楽しかったです！
It was really fun singing such an uplifting song with you!
嬉しい！かぐやも超上がった！
Aw, I'm so glad! Kaguya got super hyped too!
お互いのオリ曲を一緒に披露したわけなんですけど
We performed each other's original songs together.
マリンの『コンプレックス・プレイス』歌ってみて、どうでしたか？
How did it feel singing Marine's "Complex Place"?
え、もう、めっちゃ楽しかった！
Oh, it was so much fun!
おー、よかった！
Oh, glad to hear that!
もう歌もダンスも可愛いしさ
The song and dance are so cute,
あとコーラスもめちゃくちゃ楽しい！
and the chorus is super fun too!
楽しい！
It is!
もうみんなと一体になれる感じが本当にプリンセスにふさわしい曲だったよね！
That feeling of becoming one with everyone... it's a song truly fit for a princess, isn't it?
そうそう、プリンセスだからね、ダブルプリンセス...
Yes, yes, because we are princesses. Double princesses...
ダブルプリンセスですよ、私たち！
We are double princesses!
そうなんですよ。
That's right.
もう本当に可愛いもん。一生推します！
You're just so cute. I'll support you forever!
えい、きゅん！
Hey, Kyun!
あー、可愛い！可愛いすぎる。
Ah, so cute! Too cute!
最後に、かぐやから何かマリンのチャンネルの視聴者に向けてのメッセージや告知などありますでしょうか？
Lastly, do you have any messages or announcements for the viewers of Marine's channel, Kaguya?
はい、ございまーす！
Yes, I do!
みんな、マリンとかぐやのコラボステージを見てくれて本当にありがとう！
Everyone, thank you so much for watching Marine and Kaguya's collab stage!
かぐや、すっごく楽しかったよ！
Kaguya had so much fun!
次はツクヨミにも遊びに来てね！
Please come visit Tsukuyomi next time!
来てね！
Please come!
そして、かぐやも出てる映画『超かぐや姫』が
Also, the movie "Super Kaguya-hime" featuring Kaguya...
9月18日金曜日より特別フォーマット＆通常版、復活上映！
Will have a revival screening in special formats and the regular version starting Friday, September 18!
4DXなどの特別フォーマットにパワーアップして上映されることが決定したよ！
It's been decided that it will be screened with upgraded special formats like 4DX!
おお！新衣装！
Oh! New outfits!
そうなの！新衣装で撮影したムビチケも売ってるから、みんな絶対買ってね！
Yes! Movie tickets taken with the new outfits are also on sale, so everyone must buy one!
買わなきゃ、買わなきゃ、イェイ！イェイ！
Must buy, must buy, yay! Yay!
そして、12月に『ツクヨミ感謝祭』ってイベントでライブやるんだー！
And we are holding a live concert event in December called "Tsukuyomi Thank-you Festival"!
ライブきたー！イェイ！ワクワクする！するする！
A live concert! Yay! So exciting! Yes, it is!
みんな絶対楽しいから来てね！よろしく！
It's definitely going to be fun, so please come! Thank you!
いやー、きたこれ！本当に今日のステージ見て、みんなかぐやのパフォーマンスにメロメロになったと思うんで
Wow, this is big! After seeing today's stage, I'm sure everyone has fallen head over heels for Kaguya's performance...
もっと見たいっていう方はね、ぜひ要チェックとなっております。
So if you want to see more, definitely check it out!
いやー、マリンもね、もうかぐやの魅力に、はぁ、メロメロですよ、本当に。
Yeah, Marine is also totally smitten by Kaguya's charm, seriously.
メロメロでちょ？
You're head over heels?
メロメロでちゅ！メロメロビーム！
Head over heels! Head over heels beam!
メロメロビーム、カットされました！
The head over heels beam was cut!
でもね、違う。メロメロはメロメロでも、マリンのメロメロはかぐやを娘にしたいっていうメロメロだから。
But wait, even though I'm smitten, my kind of affection is wanting to make Kaguya my daughter.
えー！なにそれ！お姉ちゃんは？
What! What's that? What about being my big sister?
お姉ちゃんにしたいけど、娘にしたいから。
I want to be your big sister, but I really want you as a daughter.
えー、娘にしたがろう。したがろう。したがろう、娘。
Aw, let's make her a daughter, daughter, daughter.
したいけど、欲しがろう、娘。
I want to, I want you as my daughter.
いろぴーが怒るでしょ、娘。
Iropy will get angry, daughter.
そうだよ、いろぴーに怒られちゃう。
That's right, Iropy will get angry at us.
そうだよね、怒られちゃうよね。はい、いろぴーのもの。我慢します。
True, she'll get mad. Yes, you belong to Iropy. I'll hold myself back.
いや本当に、今度はぜひ、マリンもツクヨミに呼んでください！
But seriously, please invite Marine to Tsukuyomi next time!
えー、もう絶対来てよ！面白いよ、絶対！
Oh, you must come! It'll definitely be fun!
またマリンと一緒にライブしようね！
Let's perform live together again, Marine!
したいです！本当にしたい！本当に今日来てくれてありがとうございました！
I'd love to! I really want to! Thank you so much for coming today!
こちらこそありがとう！ありがとう！じゃ、またね！バイバイ！
Thank you too! Thank you! See you later! Bye-bye!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
[特報]
[Special News]
まるでバーバレラ メロメロよ
Like Barbarella, head over heels
かなりモーレツにピチピチよん
Extremely vigorous and lively
でもサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ソリチュード
But Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday solitude
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ Mine
I Love everything, I Love everything, I Love everything Mine
あ、もう無理、終わり、鬱
Ah, I can't do this anymore, it's over, depression.
全然かわいくないしさ
I'm not cute at all anyway.
めんどーくさいよね？
I'm annoying, right?
はぁ、消えたい、消えよ
*Sigh* I want to disappear, let's disappear.
え、そこがいい？
Eh, you like that about me?
嘘ばっか
You're lying.
いい女？本当？
A great woman? Really?
お宝以上？そうかな？
More than treasure? Do you think so?
最後のヒロイン？そうかニャ？
The ultimate heroine? Is that so?
弱気バイバイ スタコラサッサ
Bye-bye to being timid, running away fast!
そ、そ、そうかもね、そうだよね！
Y-Y-You might be right, that's true!
にゃーんか元気になってきた！
Meow-y how, I'm feeling energized!
サンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ソリチュード
But Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday solitude
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ Mine
I Love everything, I Love everything, I Love everything Mine
私がまた旅立つたび
Every time I set off on a journey,
鳴り響くSE
the sound effects ring out!
きゃぴきゃぴ
Kyapi kyapi!
洗脳してあげる
I'll brainwash you!
このSEで
With this SE!
もっとアイドルでいさせてよ
Let me be an idol a little longer!
きゃぴ
Kyapi!
(ヤバパパパ Shake it! Shake it!)
(Yaba-pa-pa-pa Shake it! Shake it!)
ぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃ……きゃぴ
Gya-gya-gya-gya-gya-gya... kyapi!
(1 & 2 & 3 & 4)
Shake it! Shake it!
きゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅ……きゅるん
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu... kyurun!
まるでバーバレラ メロメロよ
Like Barbarella, head over heels
かなりモーレツにピチピチよん
Extremely vigorous and lively
でもサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ソリチュード
But Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday solitude
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ Mine
I Love everything, I Love everything, I Love everything Mine
あ、もう無理、終わり、鬱
Ah, I can't do this anymore, it's over, depression.
全然かわいくないしさ
I'm not cute at all anyway.
めんどーくさいよね？
I'm annoying, right?
はぁ、消えたい、消えよ
*Sigh* I want to disappear, let's disappear.
え、そこがいい？
Eh, you like that about me?
嘘ばっか
You're lying.
いい女？
A great woman?
本当に？
Really?
お宝以上？
More than treasure?
そうかな？
Do you think so?
最後のヒロイン？
The ultimate heroine?
そうかニャ？
Is that so?
弱気バイバイ スタコラサッサ
Bye-bye to being timid, running away fast!
そ、そ、そうかもね、そうだよね！
Y-Y-You might be right, that's true!
にゃーんか元気になってきた！
Meow-y how, I'm feeling energized!
サンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ごめんねキッス
Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday sorry kiss
サンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ごめんねキッズ
Sunday Monday Sunday Monday Sunday Monday, sorry kids
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ (Wow!)
I love everything, I love everything, I love everything (Wow!)
私が瞬くたび 鳴り響く効果音
Every time I blink, the sound effects ring out
い、い、い……きゃぴ！
E, e, e... Kyapi!
洗脳してあげる 洗脳してあげる
I'll brainwash you, I'll brainwash you
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up!
Forever seventeen
接近して感電中 ズッキュンしてバタンキュー
Getting close, getting electrocuted, getting struck in the heart and passing out
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up!
萌えよSeventeen
Burn, seventeen!
セクシー×4 破廉恥バンビーナ
Sexy, sexy, sexy, sexy, shameless bambina
洗脳してあげる ×××してあげない
I'll brainwash you, I won't do XXX to you
カワイイ？ 顔がいい？ 気持ちがいい！ (I'll beat you up!)
Am I cute? Do I have a nice face? It feels so good! (I'll beat you up!)
洗脳シテアゲル アゲル アゲル
I'll brainwash you, brainwash, brainwash
もっとアイドルでいさせてよ
Let me be an idol for longer
きゃぴ
Kyapi
きゃぴきゃぴ
Kyapi-kyapi
いくつになっても
No matter how old I get
きゃぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃ……きゃぴ
Kya, kya, kya, kya, kya... Kyapi
(1 & 2 & 3 & 4) Mixer! Mixer!
(1 & 2 & 3 & 4)
きゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅ……きゅるん
Kyu, kyu, kyu, kyu, kyu... Kyurun
サンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ソリチュード
Sunday Monday Sunday Monday Sunday Monday solitude
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ 発散中
I love everything, I love everything, I love everything, releasing it all!
なんてったってなんてったってなんてったってヘヴィキュート
After all, after all, after all, I'm heavily cute!
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ (Wow!)
I love everything, I love everything, I love everything (Wow!)
来世も来々世も 浮気しちゃダメよ
Don't cheat on me, not in your next life or the one after that
きゃぴ
Kyapi
洗脳してあげる 洗脳してあげる
I'll brainwash you, I'll brainwash you
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up!
Forever seventeen
監視して崔促中 ズッキュンしてLovin' You
Monitoring you, urging you on, hitting your heart, Lovin' You
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up!
萌えよSeventeen
Burn, seventeen!
セクシー×4 ごめんねマイダーリン
Sexy, sexy, sexy, sexy, sorry my darling
洗脳してあげる もういっそ産んであげる
I'll brainwash you, I might as well give birth to you
カワイイ？ 顔がいい？ 気持ちがいい！ (I'll beat you up!)
Am I cute? Do I have a nice face? It feels so good! (I'll beat you up!)
洗脳シテアゲル アゲルッタラ ア・ゲ・ル！
I'll brainwash you, I said I'll do it, I will!
もっと I wanna beat you up!
More, I wanna beat you up!
きっと恋するだっちゃ
You'll surely fall in love, daccha!
ずっとアイドルでいさせてね
Let me be an idol forever
神様お願い きゃぴ
God, please! Kyapi!
(ヤバババ 脳 Shake it! Shake it!)
(Yabababa brain, Shake it! Shake it!)
きゃぴのび
Kyapinobi
キミたち！マリンの7周年ライブを見てくれてありがとうございました！
You guys! Thank you so much for watching Marine's 7th anniversary live!
今お披露目した新曲の「きゃぴ」は、配信終了後アニメMVが公開されます！
The anime music video for my new song "Kyapi," which I just performed, will be released after this stream ends!
マリンの考える一味とマリンの関係性と、イチャイチャが詰まったMVなので、いっぱい見て、いっぱい一緒にキュンキュンしてほしいです！
It's an MV packed with Marine's idea of the relationship between Ichimi and Marine, and lots of flirting, so I hope you watch it a lot and feel your heart throb together!
見てるうちに曲が頭から離れなくなります。洗脳させてください！
As you watch it, the song won't leave your head. Please let me brainwash you!
続いて、7周年記念グッズのお知らせです！
Next up is the announcement of the 7th anniversary commemorative goods!
まずは、B2タペストリー！こちらは今回の新衣装の水着姿を、あかさあい先生に描き下ろしていただきました！
First up is the B2 tapestry! This features my swimsuit look in this new outfit, specially illustrated by Akasa Ai-sensei!
超美しい！肉感がすごい！絶対に飾ってくださいね！
It's super beautiful! The fleshiness is amazing! You absolutely have to display it, okay?!
続いて、船長描き下ろしのランダムラバーキーホルダー！
Next, the random rubber keychains illustrated by yours truly!
デフォルメの絵柄を模索して、「これだ！」と思えるデフォルメにたどり着いたので、こんな感じで描いてみました。
I searched for a chibi art style and finally arrived at one where I thought, "This is it!" so I drew them like this.
新衣装と、まだラバーキーホルダー書いてないなっていう衣装でまとめてみました。
I put them together with the new outfit and some other outfits that I hadn't made rubber keychains for yet.
かなり可愛いバランスになったかなって、自信作なので、絶対にゲットしてくださいね！
I think the balance turned out quite cute, and it's a piece I'm proud of, so please be sure to get one!
続いてはこちら、ぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Next is this: the plushie keychain!
今回の新衣装のデザインで、ちっちゃくて可愛いぬいぐるみです。
It's a small and cute plushie based on the design of my new outfit.
お写真を撮った時に、楽しげに見えるように、めっちゃテンション高い顔に船長が描き下ろしました。
To make it look cheerful when you take photos with it, Captain specially drew a super hyper-energetic face.
楽しい撮影のときのお供にしてね。
Please make it your companion during fun photo shoots!
続いてこちら、2way推し事バッグ！
Next is this: the 2-way "Oshigoto" bag!
船長の新衣装の太ももにつけているポーチのデザインとお揃いです。
It matches the design of the pouch Captain wears on her thigh in her new outfit.
普段使いしやすく、推し活の時には推し活仕様にできる、というところを意識しました。
I designed it with the idea that it's easy for everyday use, but can be customized for fan activities when you go out.
シックなデザインなので、これなら日常使いできますよね！
Since it has a chic design, you can definitely use it in your daily life, right?!
そして、「マリンとドキドキ海水浴」っていう、ちょっとラブラブなASMRボイスもあります！
And there's also a slightly lovey-dovey ASMR voice drama called "Heart-throbbing Sea Bathing with Marine"!
ちょっとグイグイいかせてもらうんで、心の準備をしておいてください。
I'll be acting quite assertive, so please prepare your heart.
そしてそして、フルセット購入特典は、チケット風カード！
And also, the full-set purchase bonus is a ticket-style card!
昨日ね、夏の野外フェスに出演したところなので、ちょっと意識して、サマーフェスチケット風です。
Since I just performed at a summer outdoor festival yesterday, I designed it with that in mind, so it looks like a summer festival ticket.
数量限定バージョンは、直筆メッセージ入り、通常バージョンは複製直筆メッセージ入りです！
The limited-edition version comes with a hand-written message, while the regular version features a printed hand-written message!
記念に、ぜひぜひゲットしてください！
Please be sure to get it to commemorate this event!
そしてこの後は、メンバーシップ限定で、水着の3D撮影会を行います！
And after this, we'll be holding a member-only 3D swimsuit photo session!
いろんな差分をお見せするので、いっぱい堪能してくださいね。
I'll be showing various poses and variations, so please enjoy them to the fullest.
マリンのメン限はゲロ甘らしいので、これを機に、ぜひ他のメン限アーカイブと合わせて、メンバーシップいかがでしょうか？
Apparently Marine's member-only streams are sweet as sugar, so why not take this opportunity to join and check out the other archives as well?
また後日振り返り配信で、今日のいろんな裏話を聞いてください。
Also, please look forward to hearing various behind-the-scenes stories about today during a recap stream later on.
それでは行きますよ。出航ー！
Alright, here we go. Set sail!
あ〜っ
Ah!
宝鐘マリン 3D LIVE 3周年記念 / マリン新水着3Dお披露目！
[Houshou Marine 3D Live 3rd Anniversary / Marine's New Swimsuit 3D Reveal!]